runaware.com 2012-07-07

# Runaware Privacy Policy

Runaware deems privacy a central issue of Internet use. Runaware attempts to have reasonable measures in place to assure the anonymity of visitors to the Runaware web site. Runaware feels as part of responsible disclosure that Runaware web site users are aware of what information is being logged.

Runaware Privacy Policy

This policy covers how Runaware treats personal information that it collects and receives, including information related to your use of Runaware’s Online Press Center. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable such as your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

When you register, we ask for information such as your name, title, company, address, contact phone number and email. Once you register with Runaware and sign into our service, you are not anonymous to us.

Runaware uses information for the following general purposes: to track access to press materials and to provide interested press members news and information about Runaware and its products.

Runaware automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your "IP address" and the page you request. An Internet Protocol (IP) address is assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider (ISP). We use your IP address to determine the fastest route for your computer to connect to our site, report aggregate information, administer and improve the site. This log is a standard method of reporting to statistically find out which parts of our web site are visited and how long visitors spend there. We also log the type of browser and operating system you are using. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information.

Like many other commercial web sites, the Runaware web site may use a standard technology called a “cookie” to collect information about how you use the site. Cookies were originally designed to help a web site distinguish a user’s browser as a previous visitor and thus save and remember any preferences that may have been set while the user was browsing the site. A cookie is a small string of text that a web site can send to your browser. A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive, pass on computer viruses, or capture your e-mail address. Currently, web sites use cookies to enhance the user’s visit; in general, cookies can securely store a user’s ID and password, personalize home pages, identify which parts of a site have been visited or keep track of selections in a “shopping cart.” It is possible to set your browser to inform you when a cookie is being placed — this way, you have the opportunity to decide whether to accept the cookie.

At times we may request that you voluntarily supply us with personal information, such as your e-mail address, for purposes such as corresponding with us, registering at a site, making a purchase, entering a sweepstakes, or participating in an online survey.

Consent

In using this site, you agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy. Whenever you submit information via this site, you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Information Sharing and Disclosure

Runaware does not rent, sell or share personal information about your with other people or companies. Your information is only retained for reference and to verify your status as a working member of the press.

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to Runaware, such as press releases, announcements or a Runaware Newsletter without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.

Confidentiality and Security

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide assistance to the press or in order to do their jobs.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

Runaware may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your registration or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

Questions and Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us at:

Runaware, Inc  
1844 North University Drive  
Suite 203  
Fort Lauderdale, Florida 33309  
+1 [954] 302 5340

Revision date: August, 2010
